Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - CDs and DVDs: Ross photos CD,undated (Box 193, Folder 157)
  - CDs and DVDs: Ross Portraits CD,undated (Box 193, Folder 158)
  - CDs and DVDs: Sandra and UCM CD,undated (Box 193, Folder 159)
  - CDs and DVDs: Scholarship Impact Movies DVD,undated (Box 193, Folder 160)
  - CDs and DVDs: State Champs Episode #516 5 DVDs,undated (Box 193, Folder 161)
  - CDs and DVDs: Troy Strand for David Gillingham Radio Spot CD,undated (Box 193, Folder 162)
  - CDs and DVDs: Surplus Sale quicktime file DVD,undated (Box 193, Folder 163)
  - CDs and DVDs: Threads CMU / FCIT DVD,undated (Box 193, Folder 164)
  - CDs and DVDs: Lem Tucker Live the legacy Lead for life Journalism Scholarship and speaker series DVD,undated (Box 193, Folder 165)
  - CDs and DVDs: Lem Tucker Journalism scholarship DVD,undated (Box 193, Folder 166)